支票、信用卡还是现金？
Check, charge or cash?
现金
Cash.
发票写...
Make it out to...
杰克拆卸公司 图桑
Jack's Demolition. Tucson.
总数788. 30元
$788. 30.
带我吃早餐吗？
Taking me to breakfast?
不行 我要见博斯克
I can't. I'm meeting Bosko.
嗨 文森特
Hey, Vincent.
我的发夹呢？
Where are my barrettes?
我在厨房桌上见过它们
I saw them on the kitchen table.
我查看过了
I already checked.
咖啡？
Coffee?
今天不用上学？
No school today?
我爸带我去新大厦然后吃午餐
My dad's taking me to the new building and then to lunch.
到沙发垫子下找找
Try under the sofa cushions.
他已经晚了半小时
He's already a half an hour late.
他会出现还是像上次那样让她白等？
He's going to show, or stand her up like last time?
我去煮咖啡
I'll make coffee.
没时间了
Out of time.
妈妈 我的发夹不在沙发上
Mom, my barrettes are not on the couch.
戴蓝色的
Wear the blue ones.
我不想戴蓝色的 颜色不配衬
I don't want to wear the blue ones. They don't match.
- 你找过你的浴室没有？ - 我到处都找过了
- Did you check in your bathroom? - I checked everywhere!
你要我该怎办？
What do you want me to do?
去找！
Find them!
- 妈 专心点！ - 好吧 宝贝 好吧
-mom, pay attention! - All right, sweetie, all right!
爸爸要来了
Daddy's going to be here.
我来不及准备
I won't be ready!
- 我会迟到 - 不 你不会
- I'll be late. - No, you won't.
我会迟的
I will be late!
爸爸到来前能找到 只要我们一起找
Before Daddy comes, we can find them if we look together.
没事的 宝贝 没事的
It's all right, baby. It's all right.
我们会找到的 你和我 一起找
We'll find them together, you and me. We'll find them.
放心 我们找到之前他不会来的 我保证
Just relax. He won't come before we find them. I promise you.
给我再续满
Give me another refill.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
温格洛
Waingro.
迈克尔 呃？
Michael?
你们几个总是一起干？
You guys always work together?
一直如此
All the time.
密切的团队？
Real tight crew?
确实密切
Real tight.
如果这回顺利 我会考虑再做
If this works good, I'd consider going again, you know.
好的 别说话了 行么 滑头？
Yeah. Stop talking, okay, Slick?
他怎样？
How's he doing?
百份百
Hundred percent.
按预定时间
Right on schedule.
威尼斯大道右转
Made a right on Venice Boulevard.
我们离你一英里半
We're a mile and a half from you.
好
Okay.
刚刚通过第一条车道 现在离你三百码
Just crossed over the number one lane, 300 yards from you.
准备开始
Get set.
我好了
I am.
现在开始
Here we go.
“211”！我们遇劫
211!We're being held up!
- “211”警报 运钞车 - 已通知了警方
- 211 alarm. Armored car. - There's the call.
三分钟
Three minutes.
离开！
Clear!
剩80秒
Eighty seconds left!
退后！退后！
Get back! Get back!
退后！
Get back!
滑头 看见他们耳朵里流出来的东西吗？
Slick, see that shit coming out of their ears?
他们妈的听不见你说话
They can't fucking hear you!
冷静点！
Cool it!
我拿到了
I got it.
到手
Got it.
你要和我过不去
You had to fuck with me.
和我过不去？
Want to fuck with me?
你他妈干什么？ 他做了什么？
What are you doing? What did he do?
他有动作
He was making a move.
你这操蛋蠢货
Dumb motherfucker.
（古德休 救护车）
160万
A million six...
每元分4角 你可得64万
Forty cents on the dollar, $640,000 to you.
这是15万的预支
Here's $150,000 front money.
其余的两三天后给你
Get you the rest in two, three days.
这是谁的？
Who owned these?
马里布股权及投资公司
"Malibu Equity and Investments. "
罗杰·范桑特...
Roger Van Zant.
在开曼群岛拥有银行...
Owns banks in the Caymans...
替离岸贩毒的钱运作投资组合
runs investment portfolios for offshore drug money.
这一类的事
Stuff like that.
怎样？
So?
你偷了他的无记名债券
You ripped off his bearer bonds.
他买了保险
He's insured.
这就是重点 他可获百分百的保险赔偿
That's the point. He collects 100 percent from the insurance.
他是个玩家 也许他向我们买回他的债券...
He's a player. Maybe he buys his bonds back from us...
六折价购回 在百分百保险之上再赚四成
for 60 percent of their value. Makes 40 percent on top of the 100 percent.
卖回给他 你可再得32万
Sell it back to him, that's an extra $320,000 to you.
试试看
Try it on.
凯尔索来电话
Kelso called.
什么事？
About what?
他攒了一次行动 想要你看看
A score he's putting out, he wants you to look at.
我不需要他的行动 我自己有买卖
I don't need his score. I got my own.
说是很干净 而且有小八位数
Says it's clean and low eight figures.
早上九时 明天
9:00 a.m. Tomorrow.
当时出了什么事？
What happened out there?
别问
Don't ask.
找到救护车吗？
Find the ambulance?
- 离这里四条街外遭弃 - 第22街
- Dumped it four blocks from here. - 22nd Street.
他们点燃了它 烧掉了枪、衣服 所有东西
They torched it. Burned the guns, clothes, everything.
他们当时在空中
They were airborne.
他们录下了最后几秒黑白画面
They taped the last few seconds of the black- and-whites.
两星期前从弗雷斯诺偷的
Stolen from Fresno two weeks ago.
黄色皮卡车是前天在惠蒂尔被偷
Yellow pickup truck out of Whittier a day before yesterday.
你要接手这案吗 警督？
You taking this one?
还是留给分局？
Or does it stay in Division?
你觉得这像是少年团伙抢7-11便利店吗？
Does this look like gangbangers working the local 7-11 to you?
抢劫及凶杀科接手
Robbery- Homicide's taking it.
有三个汽车司机
We got three motorists.
他们都只看见戴面罩的人 他们距离远
All they saw were men with masks. They were distant.
那边的电视男 他更近些
TV man over there, however, he was closer.
他认出任何人吗？
Did he ID anybody?
他躲起来 主要是听见声音
He was hiding. He heard it mostly.
他们呢？
What about them?
根据电视男的说法 这人开始顶嘴
According to TV man, this guy started mouthing off.
聪明
Smart.
有人叫一个警卫“滑头”
Somebody called a guard "Slick. "
我认为这个人...
Now, I figure this guy...
想拿备用枪 足踝枪套
went for that hold-out piece, ankle holster.
由这儿...
From here...
砰 砰 砰...
bang, bang...bang, bang, bang.
这边
This side.
这人看起来是胸骨遭双发射击的伤口
This guy has got what appears to be a double tap- entry wound to the sternum.
头部伤口形成的纹路 灼焦的骨头 近距离 可能是处决
Tattooing around the head wound, scorched bones, close range. Probably executed.
160万的无记名债券
It was a million six in bearer bonds.
他们没理会零散现金
They ignored the loose cash.
因为他们没时间 他们按点行动
'Cause they had no time. They were on a clock.
意味着他们知道我们对“211”的反应时间
Which means they knew our response time to a 211...
听我们的广播 把车截停 进入...
had our air, immobilized it, entered...
逃走 在三分钟以内
escaped in under three minutes.
这是好地点 有良好逃走路线
It's a good spot here. We got good escape routes.
两条高速公路...
Two freeways...
在四分一英里之内
within a quarter of a mile.
交通摄像机？
Traffic video camera?
可能给弄坏了 总之查一下
Probably disabled. Check it anyway.
你认出手法吗？
You recognize the M. O?
手法...
M. O...
就是他们很厉害
is that they're good.
一看到事情激化 他们都犯下一级谋杀罪 在杀了两个警卫后...
Once it escalated into a murder- one beef for all of them, after they killed two guards...
他们便不再迟疑
they didn't hesitate.
崩了第三名警卫 因为...没什么区别
Popped guard number three because...what difference does it make?
为什么要留下一个活证呢？
Why leave a living witness?
落下点火星子 这些人就会炸锅
Drop of a hat, these guys will rock- and-roll.
定向炸药
The shape charge.
定向炸药表明他们是技术专家
The shape charge indicates that they are technically proficient.
专业到在途中下手
Proficient enough to go in on the prowl.
我们找找最近令人棘手的盗窃要案
Let's look for recent high- line burglaries that mystify us.
找FBI查“滑头”这绰号 你会得到本电话簿（很长）
Run "Slick" as an alias to the FBI. You're gonna get the phone book.
还是查一查 谁运送的无记名债券？
Do it anyway. Who's moving the bearer bonds?
查查惯常收赃人 你和我查库泽马诺和特瑞纳
Check the usual fences. You and I will check Cuzomano and Torena.
我要你查高德斯丁和阿尔法罗
I want you to take Goldstein and Alfaro.
和鉴证科紧密合作
Hang in with Forensics.
问爆破组 我要那爆炸物
From the bomb squad, I want the explosive.
运气好 如果它是罕见的 我们可以追查来源
If we're lucky, it's exotic. We can trace the sale.
你别伸手进那人的口袋
Get your hand out of that man's pocket.
有谁要派吗？
Anyone want some pie?
我要上厕所
Gotta go to the john.
我不得不动手 他有动作 我不得不动手
I had to get it on. He was making a move. I had to get it on.
他那份在车上 我均摊拿出了我们的...
Split's in the car. I took out of ours evenly...
...为了补偿他的
to make up for his full end...
因为我想付清钱 立刻摆脱这杂种
'cause I want to pay off and get rid of this motherfucker right now.
慢着！
Hold it!
其余的呢？
Where's the rest?
我们迟到了 你打扮得很漂亮
We're late. You look too good to go out.
我想在这儿扑倒你
I'll just jump you right here.
- 在哪里？ - 还给赌马经纪了 宝贝
- Where is it? - Squared the bookies, baby.
几天后还会有钱 别心焦了 我们迟到了
There's more in a couple of days, so don't sweat it. We're late.
得了吧
Come on.
你跟我开玩笑呢吧
You gotta be kidding me.
亲爱的...
Honey...
为了8千元你不值得冒这些险 高风险高回报
it ain't worth the risks you take for $8,000. Like in "Risk versus reward. "
我们走吧
Let's go.
拿你的外衣
Get your coat.
谈话毫无意义 你是个长不大的孩子
There is no point talking. You're a child growing older.
什么意思？
What does that mean?
意思是我们毫无进展 不像真正过日子的成年人那样...
We're not making forward progress like real grown- up adults living our lives...
因为我嫁给一个好赌的瘾君子 他不听劝
because I married a gambling junkie who won't listen.
莎琳 他妈的上车
Charlene, get in the fucking car.
我这是在干吗？
What am I doing in this rap?
你不用！
You're not!
你要我怎么做？
What you want for me?
出门的时候把存折和车钥匙留在厨房吗？
leave the bank book and the car keys in the kitchen on the way out the door?
- 我们走吗？ - 别废话了 多明尼克跟我走
- Are we going? - Keep that crap. Dominick comes with me.
想都别想...
Don't even think about...
是我 告诉我阿尔伯特·特瑞纳回电话了
Yeah. Tell me Albert Torena called back.
阿尔伯特·特瑞纳给文森特打过电话吗？
Albert Torena call Vincent?
没有
No.
报告来了
Report came in.
爆炸物是炸药 用于拆毁...
The explosive was Dy- Ex, used in demolition.
你可凭驾照在内华达...
You can pick it up in Nevada...
亚利桑拿、新墨西哥州买到
Arizona, New Mexico.
太普通难以追查来源
Too common to trace a sale.
真是好极了
That's wonderful.
你没事吧？
You all right?
怎么了？你去了哪儿？
What happened? Where have you been?
工作
Work.
萝伦的父亲来过吗？
Lauren's dad show up?
没来电话没出现 我们等你到十时半
Didn't call didn't show. We waited for you till 10:30.
这人知不知道这孩子状况如何？
Now, does this guy have any idea what's going on with this kid?
我不知道
I don't know.
他妈的混蛋
Fucking jerk.
她还好吗？
Is she okay?
她整天在房间里
She's been in her room all day.
所以 不 她不好 我也不好
So, no, she's not okay. Neither am I.
我做了晚餐...
I made dinner...
给我俩 四小时前
for us, four hours ago.
每一次我设法在我俩间维持一贯的情绪
Every time I try to maintain a consistent mood between us...
你就退却
you withdraw.
我有三具躺在人行道上的死尸...
I got three dead bodies on a sidewalk...
在威尼斯大道 贾丝汀
off Venice Boulevard, Justine.
对不起...
I'm sorry...
如果这可恶的...
if the goddamn...
鸡...
chicken...
烤过了头
got overcooked.
要咖啡吗？
Coffee, sir?
好的
Please.
请把奶递给我
Will you pass the cream?
谢谢
Thanks.
你买了什么？
What'd you get?
什么？
What?
你看什么书？
What are you reading?
关于金属的书
Book about metals.
钛的应力折断
Stress Fractures in Titanium.
你做什么工作的？
What kind of work do you do?
女士 你为什么对我读什么做什么有兴趣？
Lady, why are you so interested in what I read or what I do?
我时不时在店里见到你
I've seen you in the store from time to time.
什么店？
What store?
亨尼西与英格思书店 我在那工作
Hennessey and Ingalls. I work there.
要是你不想跟我交谈 没关系
If you don't want to talk to me, it's okay.
抱歉打扰了你
I'm sorry I bothered you.
我不是有意无礼 我没认出你
I didn't mean to be rude. I didn't recognize you.
我做金属行业 我是销售员
I work in metals. I'm a salesman.
我名叫尼尔
My name's Neil.
我叫伊迪
I'm Eady.
你喜欢在那里工作？
You like working there?
当然
Sure.
我有折扣 而且有一个区全是我领域的书
I get a discount and there's a whole section of books in my area.
是哪一领域？
What area?
平面设计
Graphic design.
我晚上设计信纸及商标...
I do letterheads and logotypes at night and...
白天在书店工作直至能藉此谋生
the store's a day job until I get enough going.
你为谁设计呢？
Who do you do that for?
一家餐厅
A restaurant.
我做他们的菜单
I did their menus
还有...
and...
一家小唱片公司
a small record label.
CD
CDs.
目前已设计了两张
I've done two so far.
你上学校学的吗？
You go to school for that?
是的
Yeah.
我念过帕森斯
I went to Parsons.
在哪儿？
Where's that?
纽约市
New York City.
你在这儿住了多久？
How long you been here?
大约一年
About a year.
喜欢这儿吗？
You like it?
不算喜欢 我主要是为工作才来这儿
Not really. I'm mostly here for the work.
你住在附近？
Live in this neighborhood?
不 我住在...差不多日落广场上面
No, I live kind of above Sunset Plaza.
实际上是...是我租的一所小房子
It's actually kind of a...it's a little house I rent.
颇为破旧 但景观非常非常美
And it's kind of rundown, but a beautiful, beautiful view.
你呢？
What about you?
我住在这儿
I live up here.
很有趣
That's very funny.
你的家人原本来自哪里？
Where's your family from originally?
是苏格兰- 爱尔兰裔
They're Scots- lrish.
他们移民到阿帕拉契亚...16世纪晚期
They emigrated to Appalachia...in the late 1700s.
你从哪儿来？
Where are you from?
湾区（旧金山）
The Bay area.
家人在那里？
Your folks there?
母亲很久前死了 我父亲...
My mother died a long time ago, and my father...
我不知他在哪儿
I don't know where he is.
我有个兄弟在什么地方
Got a brother somewhere.
你的家庭关系紧密 我敢说
You have a tight family. I can tell.
是啊
Yeah.
对吗？
Right?
你说得对
You're right.
光明之城
City of lights...
在斐济 有一种...
In Fiji, they have these...
霓虹光的海藻 每年浮出水面一次
iridescent algae that come out once a year in the water.
就是那边那种样子
That's what it looks like out there.
你去过？
You been there?
没有 我有一天会去的
No, I'm going there some day.
你常旅游？
You travel a lot?
是的
Yeah.
旅游令你寂寞？
Travelling makes you lonely?
我单独 我并不...
I'm alone. I am not...
寂寞
lonely.
你呢？
You?
真的寂寞
Real lonely.
阿尔伯特！
Albert!
糟糕！
Shit!
阿尔伯特
Al- bert
文森 老兄你干嘛来这找我？你疯了吗？
Vinsen, man, why are you here for me? You crazy?
- 这里不是迪斯尼乐园 - 你昨晚该回我电话的
- This ain't Disneyland. - You were supposed to get back to me last night.
你他妈去哪儿了？
Where the fuck you been?
我无法脱身 文森 你知道
I couldn't break free, Vinsen, you know.
我们来侵犯他的狗屁民权吧
Let's violate his ass right now.
我帮忙你...
I do for you...
你却不帮我 是这样吗？
you don't do for me, is that it?
听着 伙计 我发誓 我整晚在外面 像个斗牛士一样东躲西藏
Listen, man. I swear, I was out all night. I'm hidden like a Flamingo matador.
此事和我无关
That's got nothing to do with me.
我干得顺利 我正在给你搞线索什么的
I'm cutting it smooth. I'm generating leads and shit for you.
我很活跃的 老兄
I'm a dancer, man, you know
你胡扯
You bullshit.
我一整天传呼你个屁人 我受不了他妈的传呼
I paged your ass all day. I can't stand fucking paging.
你是瘾君子 又注射脱氧麻黄素了？
You're a speed freak, jacking methamphetamine again.
老兄 你的同情心呢？这是滥用药物问题
Where's your empathy? It's a substance abuse problem.
同情心在昨天 今天你在浪费我他妈的时间
Empathy was yesterday. Today you're wasting my motherfucking time.
- 文森...- 你恋爱了？
- Vinsen...- You fall in love?
说吧 你昨晚是不是恋爱了...
Come on. Did you fall in love last night...
- 然后到别处去？ - 文森
- ...and went off somewhere? - Vinsen
告诉我好了 我会接受的 我会买账
Just tell me that, I'll settle for it. I'll buy then.
把你弄到的都给我！
Give me all you got!
我发誓 老兄 我哥哥理查德会跟你说
I swear, man. My brother Richard's going to talk to you.
我听见理查德？
I heard Richard?
- 他会和你说的 - 理查德？
- He's going to talk to you. - Richard?
- 理查德 - 理查德？
- Richard. - Richard?
他会见你 老兄 我发誓 今晚
He's gonna meet you, man. I swear, tonight.
他不在这儿 对吗？
He's not here, is he?
不 他今晚会见你
No, he'll meet you tonight.
今晚？现在不行吗？
Tonight? What happened to now?
我恳求他了 因为我知道你今早会到来
I implored him because I knew you was coming this a.m.
胡说
Bullshit.
我发誓 他说不行...
I swear. He said no...
因为他在凤凰城
'cause he in Phoenix.
等我到了凤凰城...
"By the time I get to Phoenix
他会起程...
"He'll be rising
他可能留下张字条...
"He'll probably leave a note
贴在门上
"Right on the door"
我最多只能给你安排在今晚
Tonight's the best I can do for you.
知道不 他在艾华瓦度街BJ夜总会见你
You know. He'll meet you at BJ's on Alvarado.
凌晨两点
At 2:00 a.m.
去就行
Be there.
你也要到
You be there too.
文森 我不能去 老兄 我有事要办
Vinsen, I can't be there, man. I got things to do.
我有事办 要到别处去
I got things to do, I got places to be.
去那
Be there.
别浪费我他妈的时间！
Don't waste my motherfucking time!
是什么？
What is it?
是一家银行
It's a bank.
它星期四会存现金 以便分发各分行...
It depos cash on Thursday for distribution to all the other branches...
应付星期五的薪金支票
to cover Friday payroll checks.
所以星期四 总行大有机会
So on Thursdays, the command branch has got a full whack.
在途中还是硬来？
On the prowl or strong?
硬来 由正门
Strong. Through the door.
多少人？
How many guys?
大约四或三个 加上一个司机 你走进去 搞掂他们 走出来
About four, or three, plus a driver. You walk in, knock 'em over, walk out.
你要预支十万 事成后分一成？
You want $100,000 in advance against a ten- percent cut for that?
听着像是西部牛仔劫银行
Sounds like a cowboy score.
他们按抢劫警铃 我得在警察出现前离开 这算什么？
They hit the hold-up alarms, I gotta get out before the cops show. What is that?
他们可以按三个抢劫警钟
They hit three hold-up alarm systems.
两个固定的和一个移动的...
Two Telco and a cellular.
但讯号哪儿也传不出去 因为...
But the signals aren't going anywhere because...
之前一晚...
the night before...
你潜进去...
you cut in...
修改警报系统的电脑...
and trick out the alarm system computer...
把它...
to turn itself...
及录像设备...
and the video recorders off...
在你下手前20分钟关掉
20 minutes before you enter.
建筑及电路蓝图？
Architectural, electrical plans?
我有
I got that.
我已经让人做好主板 接驳中央处理器
I got the boards already built. They go into the CPU.
估价是多少？
What's the estimate?
1210万到1220万
12. 1, 12. 2 million.
你说服我了
You're on.
恭喜
Congratulations.
我来给你点头绪 我是怎么估算这笔钱的
Let me give you a little idea of where my estimates come from.
没人知道货是你的
Nobody knew the merch was yours.
我的办法 你从保险公司得到百分百赔偿...然后从我们这拿回债券
My way, you get 100 percent from the insurance company...take the bonds back from us...
以美元支付的60% 而你自己再赚40%
at 60 cents on the dollar and make yourself another 40 percent.
这运作没漏下一个环节 咱们都明白
The operation doesn't skip a beat. We all make out.
当然 你的交易成了
Sure, you got a deal.
好 因为如果有人不高兴那就没有利益分成
Good, because there's no percentage if everyone gets upset.
对 让你的人给我打电话 我们安排会面
Yeah. You have your man call me and we'll set the meet.
好 没问题
Yeah, okay.
高兴和你通话
Nice talking to you.
你要和这些人交易？
You gonna deal with these guys?
道上的说法 我可以偷自己的东西吗？
Word's on the street it's okay to steal my stuff.
我会杀了这班婊子养的
I'm going to kill these sons of bitches.
叫哈利给我加那利群岛离岸的电子表格
Have Harry bring me the spreadsheets for Canary Island's Offshore.
这些并不算是估计 是实在数字
That's not really an estimate. Those are exact figures.
我有银行过去两月现金流的打印本
I have a printout of the bank's cash flow for the past two months.
你怎么得到的资料？
How'd you get this information?
送上门的
Just comes to you.
这东西在空中传播
This stuff just flies through the air.
如今这类信息到处发送 你只要抓取就行
It's just beamed out all over the place. You just have to grab it.
我懂得如何抓取
I know how to grab it.
好了 这里
Okay, here we go.
1390万
13. 9 million.
- 我同意了 - 好
- I bought it. - Good.
我没说错吧
What did I tell you?
拿着
Here.
我们成了 致电范桑特 收钱吧
We're on. Call Van Zant, collect the money.
他怎样？
How is he?
他是生意人
He's a businessman.
克里斯在我这里
Chris is at my place.
怎么了？
What's wrong?
夫妻的事
Husband and wife stuff.
我让他睡醒再说
I'll let him sleep it off.
你怎么了？
What happened to you?
你什么时候去买点家具？
When will you get some furniture?
等我有时间
When I get around to it.
莎琳要离开我
Charlene's gonna leave me.
为什么？
Why?
冰箱里吃的不够了
Not enough steaks in the freezer.
我们做的还不够？
With everything we've been doing?
维加斯和超级碗把我掏干了
Vegas and the Super Bowl cleaned me out.
你什么时候去找个女人？
When you gonna get an old lady?
等我有时间
When I get around to it.
你外头有什么事吗
You got something else on the side?
没有固定的
Nothing regular.
她外头有什么事吗？
She got something else on the side?
- 没有 - 你肯定？
- No - You sure?
对 我肯定
Yeah, I'm sure.
我不知道你在搞什么
I don't know what you're doing.
像吉米说的 “你想在街头混吗？
As Jimmy said, " You want to be making moves on the street?
“要没有牵挂 生活中不能有任何...
"Have no attachments. Allow nothing to be in your life...
“...你在30秒内不能离开的事物 一旦你在街角认出危险 ”
"...that you can't walk out on in 30 seconds if you spot the heat around the corner. "
记得吗？
Remember that?
对我来说 太阳都随着她起落 老兄
For me, the sun rises and sets with her, man.
是吗？
Yeah?
是
Yeah.
好吧
Okay.
我们从范桑特那儿取到钱...
We take delivery of cash from Van Zant...
然后为劫银行的事存钱给凯尔索
then I drop a deposit on Kelso for this bank.
银行？什么银行？
Bank? What bank?
那件白金的事呢？都快成事了
What about the platinum thing? It's ready to fall.
那也会进行 然后劫银行
That goes too. Then the bank.
要吃早餐吗？
Want some breakfast?
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
没事
Yeah, sugar.
是真的
For real.
我会好好做
I'll do good.
一会儿见
I'll see you later.
你是索伦戈？
You Solenko?
唐·布里丹
Don Breedan.
格里森 我的假释官 告诉我来这里 你会有工作给我
Grierson, my parole officer, told me to come by here, see if you had a job for me.
你对这类工作熟悉吗？
You're familiar with this kind of operation?
我烧烤很出色的
I'm a great grill man.
好啊 恭喜你了
Good. Good for you.
你拖洗厕所 洗碗碟 收拾桌子还有倒垃圾
You'll mop the toilets, hit the dishwasher, bus tables and empty the garbage.
让我难做 我就报告你藏毒、酗酒或偷窃
Give me a hard time, I'll report you loaded, drunk or stealing.
我会很快让你违反条例回去
I'll violate you back fast.
你薪金的25%给我当回佣
Twenty- five percent of your take- home kicks back to me.
游戏规则 打给格里森查问 后面换衣服
Rules of the game. Call Grierson, check it out. Change in the back.
你还等什么？
What are you waiting for?
马里布股票及投资
Malibu Equity and Investments.
罗杰·范桑特
Roger Van Zant.
请等一等
Please hold.
我是罗杰·范桑特
This is Roger Van Zant.
我有些东西要拿
I'm supposed to get something.
给我你的号码 有人会从另一线路打给你
Someone will call you back from another line.
８１８- １３３ - ６０８９...
我有东西给你 森汀内拉有一家露天影院 明天2:30
I got a package for you. There's a drive- in on Centinela. 2:30 tomorrow.
派一个人 独自来
Just send one man, alone.
- 那人是谁？ - 谁也不是
- Who was that guy? - Nobody.
我要知道他是谁！他是谁？
I gotta know who he is! Who is he?
他谁也不是 尼尔
He's nobody, Neil.
他是拉斯维加斯的一个合法售酒人 亚伦·马西亚诺
He's a legit liquor salesman from Las Vegas. Alan Marciano.
克里斯会跟你和好的
Chris's gonna straight up with you.
- 太迟了！我厌烦他了！ - 闭嘴
- It's too late! I'm sick of him! - Shut up!
事情是这样 你给克里斯最后一次机会 以后如果他搞砸了...
Here's the deal. You'll give Chris one last shot. After that, he fucks up,
我本人会资助你找地方住 你想去哪里都行
then I will finance setting you up myself... on my own, anywhere you want.
多明尼克会跟你
Dominick will go with you.
我说话算数 但现在...
And my word counts. But right now...
你要给他机会
you will give him the chance.
清洗一下 回家去
Clean up, go home.
清洗一下 回家！
Clean up, go home!
把你的钱给我
Give me your money.
你会因此而没命的
You'll get smoked with that shit.
不会是你
Won't be you.
他一个人进来了 让他过去
He's coming in alone. Send him through.
好 行
Yeah. Got it.
文森特 嘿 老兄
Vincent, hey, man.
文森特 嘿 这是我哥哥理查德 文森特
Vincent. Hey, this is my brother, Richard. Vincent.
- 理查德 - 好了
- Richard - It's all right.
你有什么消息给我？
What have you got for me?
谈正题前 有那么一个团伙在偷车 沙滩附近
Before we even get into that, there's this crew ripping rides all along the beach.
明白？在一家"都市人"样品装饰店后面
All right? Now, in the back of a trim sample uranite...
这周末要是有人想去小小探访一下...
somebody wants to pay a little visit this weekend...
可能会找到两辆Turbo和一辆911 Slope
they might find two Turbos and a 911 slope.
你要为自己除掉竞争对手吗？
You looking to rid yourself of your competition?
我是个好市民
I'm a good citizen.
我是唐老鸭
I'm Donald Duck.
你有事要告诉我还是怎的？
So, you got something to tell me or what?
这么说好了 兄弟
Check this out, cuz.
我怎么知道 如果我说出你想知道的事...
How do I know if I tell you what you need to know...
...你就会做我想做的事
that you gonna do what the fuck I need to get done.
理查德
Richard.
老兄 汉纳是个直截了当的人 我们一直合作
Man, Hanna is a straight up man. We do business all the time.
我不是你的兄弟 你这杂种耗子
I ain't your cuz, you rat motherfucker.
你知道 是因为我说了
And you know because I say so...
要在我听到你他妈要告诉我什么之后
after I hear what the fuck you got to tell me!
我操 老兄
Fuck you, man
你明白我说的吗？
You understand what i'm saying?
我说出来会被杀的
I'd get killed for telling you.
你溜狗时也会被杀
You'd get killed walking your doggie!
好吧 老兄
All right, man...
有一个人曾跟我关在一起...
there was a cat I was locked up with.
服刑两三年 他出狱后我碰见他
Did a couple of two, three years. He got out. I ran into him.
那又怎样？
And so?
他是个搞行动的大能人
He's a big fiend for action.
要是他什么也没说 我也什么都不会想 可...
Now, if he'd have said nothing, I'd have thought nothing, but...
他一遍一遍的对我说 他没做过什么事...
he goes on and on, running down to me how he ain't done nothing...
而且没在做什么事 全是这些废话
and nothing's been going on and all this bullshit.
所以就在那会儿我就知道...
Right then and there I know...
这人干了什么坏事
this cat's got something going down.
相当他妈的大案
Pretty fucking great.
阿尔伯特 你怎么回事了？
Albert, what's wrong with you?
你拉我来这里 这样浪费我的时间
You drag me here, waste my time like this.
你在街上见到一个有前科的家伙？
You saw a guy on the street who's an ex-con?
正是
That's right.
那么我是...
Well, I am...
他妈的喜出望外
over- fucking- whelmed.
凭这个你想得到什么 初级联邦调查局徽章？
What do you want for that, a junior G-man badge?
瞧 老兄 你会不会查保时捷的事？
Look here, man. You gonna make the call on them Porches or what?
他跟我说笑吗？
Is he kidding me?
我告诉你
I'm telling you:
滑头可他妈不是说笑的 老兄
Slick is no motherfucking joke, man.
你知道我的意思吗？他挣双份
You know what i'm saying? He's double time.
说什么？
Say what?
- 什么？ - 你说“滑头” 是什么意思？
- What? - "Slick. " What does that mean?
滑头 他常叫别人为“滑头”
"Slich". That's what he calls people: "Slick. "
跟我讲讲他
And, tell me about him.
大约六尺高...
About 6 feet tall...
许多监狱纹身
lots of jailhouse tats.
刺了一头大孔雀在这儿
Got a big- ass peacock right here.
他叫什么名字？
What's his name?
切里托
Cheritto.
迈克尔·切里托
Michael Cheritto.
自1976年起被捕33次
Thirty- three busts since 1976.
11次是持械行劫 3次被定罪
Eleven for armed robbery, three convictions.
判刑3至5年 在阿提卡两年
Two out of a three- to- five year beef in Attica.
3年在马里昂
Three years in Marion.
因误杀罪在福尔松服刑5年
Five years in Folsom off a knock- back to involuntary manslaughter.
案底两英寸厚
Jacket's two inches thick.
好 现在有谁在那边？
Okay. Who do I have there now?
杜拉克和我 老板 还有施瓦茨
Drucker and me. And Schwartz.
告诉SIS我要全面监视 就是24小时
Tell SIS I want full surveillance. That's 24 hours.
围着钟转 日夜不停
Round the clock, day and night.
我们不停止 一周七天运转
We never close. Open 7 days a week.
监听汽车 房子 工作
Bug the car, the house, the works.
他有所行动或逗留 比如去餐馆 我要跟他在一起行动坐卧的人的照片
When he moves or sits, like in a restaurant... I want pictures of who he moves and sits with.
然后你们调查他们 他们有案底 我要看见他们跟谁一起行动坐卧
Then you guys run makes on them. They got jackets, I want to see who them move with who they sit with.
我要明晚之前执行
I want it up and running by tomorrow night.
把手放在我看到的地方
Put your hands where I can see them.
我会告诉你做什么及怎样去做
I tell you what to do. I tell you how to do it.
现在 只用你的右手 只准右手...
Now, with your right hand only, your right hand only...
拿出包裹 把它扔进来
take the package and throw it in here.
你后面 右边
Behind you. On the right.
罗杰·范桑特
Roger Van Zant.
是谁？
Who's this?
你知道是谁
You know who this is.
对 我知道
Yes, I do.
我派了一个人送包裹
I sent a guy to deliver the package.
他没来电话 一切妥当吧？
He didn't call. Is everything okay?
我告诉你 忘掉那笔钱
I tell you what, forget the money.
什么？
What?
忘掉那笔钱
Forget the money.
那是一大笔钱 你在干吗？你什么意思“忘掉那笔钱”
It's a lot of money. What are you doing? What do you mean, "forget the money"?
我在干吗？我在对着空话筒说话
What am I doing? I'm talking to an empty telephone.
我不明白
I don't understand.
因为电话的另一端是个死人
'Cause there is a dead man on the other end of this line.
你喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
看我的戒指
Look at my ring.
你知道吗？
Did you know?
你疯了
You are insane.
喜欢吗？
Do you like it?
- 很漂亮 - 很好
- It's beautiful. - It's good.
别问他哪儿得来的
Don't ask him where he got it.
你长大后想做什么？
What do you want to be when you grow up?
我不知道
I don't know.
像我一样
Just like me.
我也不知道
I don't know either.
你好
Hello?
是我
It's me.
我在想你是否会来电话
I was wondering if you'd call.
我一直忙
I've been busy.
我可见你吗？
Can I see you?
我害怕那只是...
I was afraid that was just...
一夜情
the one night.
对我来说不是
Not for me, it wasn't.
我也不是
Yeah, me neither.
我可来吗？
Can I fall by?
可以
Yeah.
一会儿见
I'll see you in a little bit.
好的
All right.
可恶的会议
Goddamn convention.
- 哪个是滑头？ - 魁梧的那个
- Which one's Slick? - The wide one.
我们有两个传送器
We got two transmitters.
一个在轮舱里 后备的在防火墙里
One's in the wheel well, backup's in the firewall.
是我们的车
Here we are.
跟尼尔道晚安了吗？
Did you say good night to Neil?
金发的是克里斯·施赫勒斯
The blond is Chris Shiherlis.
SIS派人循环盯梢他 还给房子电话接了一条线
SIS has got a revolving tail and hung a wire on the house phone.
切里托的车三次驶过贵重金属仓库
Cheritto's cruised the precious-metals depository three times.
白金、银和一些金条
Platinum, silver, and some bullion.
萨米和我认为是他们的下一行动
Sammy and I think that's going to be their next score.
那独行者是谁？
Who's the loner?
我们第一次见他
First time we're seeing him.
还没开始跟踪他
We're not on him yet.
立即开始吧
Get on it.
不管他们下次行动在哪里搞 等这些家伙再走出门时...
When these guys walk out the door of whatever score they're gonna take next...
他们会得到终生难遇的惊喜
they're gonna have the surprise of a lifetime.
宝贝 该走了
Baby, time to go.
我令你很开心 对吧？
Showed you a good time, didn't I?
你很棒
You fly.
你不错
You cool.
你骗我 我总是看得出别人骗我
You're lying to me. I can always tell when people lie to me.
我没说谎
I ain't lying.
你是条猛犬
You a hot dog.
合格的牛圈骑手
A regular rodeo rider.
这是我一生里搞得最狂野的一次
And this was the monster fuck of my young life.
现在 我得回到街上去了 甜心
Now, I got to get my ass street- side, sugar.
你没有说实话的作风
You don't have a truth- telling style.
你说什么？
What are you talking about?
你不知道这是什么
You don't know what this is.
是拿镰刀的死神来探望你
The Grim Reaper's visiting with you.
你去了哪儿？
Where have you been?
鹈鹕湾的特别收容所
SHU at Pelican Bay.
以及福尔松监狱B翼
And Folsom, B- wing.
我是一个牛仔...
I am a cowboy...
正在找大买卖
looking for anything heavy.
比利说来找你
Billy said to come see you.
因此我来了
That is why I am here.
你何不给这人打电话？
Why don't you call this guy?
这人经常招人入伙
This guy's always putting guys on.
谢谢
Thank you.
你们天生一对
You're perfect for each other.
我念小学时认识一个人
I knew a guy in grade school.
他叫拉乌尔...什么的
His name was Raoul...whatever.
你可以把他的手指一只只叠起来
You could take his fingers and fold them over each other.
他可把眼睑向外翻...
He'd turn his eyelids inside out...
我没法把手从你身上拿开 是真的
I can't keep my hands off you. That's the truth.
你吸引的地方在于你那...
That's what's so wonderful about you in that...
兽性的方式
bestial sort of way.
女人
Woman.
这最好是惊天动地的事
This better be earth- shattering.
为拉乌尔干杯
This is to Raoul.
我是文森特·汉纳
Yeah, Vincent Hanna.
我们发现她时是这样的
Here's how we found her.
多大？
How old?
十六七岁 在此约六小时
16, 17. Been here about six hours.
她怎么死的？
How'd she die?
头部给重击 跟其他人一样 大脑血肿
Beat her head in, same as the others. Cerebral hematoma.
那是谁？
Who's that?
母亲及兄弟姐妹 我猜
Mother and siblings, I guess.
他们来干什么鬼？
What the hell are they doing here?
已经搞乱了 内部有人认识这女孩 通知了家人
It's fucked up. Somebody inside knew the girl and called the family.
好吧 我们开始
Okay, let's go.
不错
Nice.
直觉告诉我 化验精液会发现是同一个人...
My intuition says the check on the semen will show it's the same guy...
因此是连环谋杀案 最终由你的组调查
so it's a series and ending up in your court.
治安官有头绪吗？
Sheriff's getting anywhere?
还没有
Not yet.
放开我！
Get off of me!
天啊！
Oh, my God!
她在哪儿？
Where is she?
冷静！冷静！
Easy, easy, easy.
求你 别这样
Please, come on.
没事的 没事的
It's okay. It's okay.
我的孩子呢？她在哪？
Where is my baby? Where is she?
我要知道出了什么事
I need to know what happened.
我猜是惊天动地了
I guess the earth shattered.
你为何不让博斯克送你回家？
So why didn't you let Bosko take you home?
我也不想扫他们的兴
I didn't want to ruin their night too.
是什么事？
What was it?
你不想知道的
You don't want to know.
我想知道你铁青的脸孔后面藏着什么
I'd like to know what's behind that grim look on your face.
我不会这么做 你知道的 我们走吧
I don't do that. You know it. Let's go.
你从没告诉我 我会被拒诸事外
You never told me I'd be excluded.
我们刚在一起时我告诉过你...
I told you when we hooked up...
你不得不和我分享...
that you were gonna have to share me...
这星球上所有的坏人和丑行
with all the bad people and all the ugly events on this planet.
而我愿意那种分享...
And I bought into that sharing...
因为我爱你
because I love you.
我爱你发胖、秃头、有钱、没钱
I love you fat, bald, money, no money,
开巴士
driving a bus.
我不在乎
I don't care.
但你一定要出现
But you have got to be present
像个普通人那样 某些时候
like a normal guy, some other time.
那是分享 这不是分享 这是残余
That's shareing. This is not shareing. This is leftover
我懂了 我应该这么做对吗 回家后说：
I see. What I should do is come home and say:
“嗨 亲爱的 你知道吗？我今天走进一所房子...
"Hi, honey, guess what? I walked into this house today...
“有个吸毒的混蛋 刚用微波炉炸了他的婴儿...
"...where this junkie asshole just fried his baby in a microwave...
“因他哭得太吵闹 让我和你分享这件事吧
"...because he was crying too loud, so let me share that with you.
"来 让我们分享此事 而在分享时...
Come on, let's share that and in sharing it...
"我们莫名其妙就可以 净化和驱散所有那些邪恶的狗屎 ”
"...we'll somehow cathartically dispel all that heinous shit. "
对吗？
Right?
错
Wrong.
你知道为什么？
You know why?
因为你更喜欢日常公事
'Cause you prefer the normal routine.
我们搞 你失去说话之力
We fuck and you lose the power of speech.
因为我得保持住我的焦虑
'Cause I got to hold onto my angst.
我保存它...
I preserve it...
因为我需要它 它让我保持敏锐 坐立不安
because I need it. It keeps me sharp, on the edge.
我必须待在那
Where I gotta be.
你没有和我生活
You don't live with me.
你在死人的残骸中生活
You live among the remains of dead people.
你查看地形
You read the terrain.
你找寻逝去的迹象...
You search for signs of passing...
找猎物的气味...
for the scent of your prey...
然后追捕他们
and then you hunt them down.
这是你唯一投入的事
That's the only thing you're committed to.
剩余的 是你走过后留下的烂摊子
The rest is the mess you leave as you pass through.
我不明白的是 我为何摆脱不了你
What I don't understand is why I can't cut loose of you.
嘿 莉莉
Hey, Lily
走吧 宝贝
Let's go, baby.
我见过那经理了
I met the manager.
那是老板吗？
Is that the boss?
让我坐牢的事情 那个混蛋每天都在做
I did time for what that motherfucker does every day.
你能不能忍着 直到我们给你找到新工作吗？
Can you just handle it till we find you something new?
你能做到吗？
Can you do that?
没有我忍受不了的艰难时刻
Ain't a hard time been invented that I cannot handle.
你为何和我一起 莉莉？
What you're hanging with me for?
因为我以你为荣
Because I'm proud of you.
你以我为荣？
You're proud of me?
你以我什么鬼东西为荣？
Why the hell are you proud of me?
回家吧
Come on home.
你在那里做什么？
What were you doing there?
我滑雪
I was skiing.
我试着滑雪
I was trying to ski.
人们去那里就是做这个 你去滑雪...
That's what people do there. You go skiing...
你...你结识别人
and you meet people.
你试着开心
You try to have a good time.
- 你开心吗？ - 没
- Did you have a good time? - No.
为什么？
Why not?
我不擅结识别人
I'm not good at meeting people.
你认识了我
You met me.
我没加细想事情便发生了
That happened without my thinking about it.
因此我可能是...
Which is why I probably...
不 是因为你很好
No, it's because you are fine.
伊迪 和我一起离开一阵子
Take off with me for a while.
去哪？
Where?
新西兰
New Zealand.
何时？
When?
我得单独走 你可以在那里跟我会合
I have to go separate. You can meet me there.
但我的工作
But my job...
我有钱 你不需要钱
I got money. You don't need money.
你可以开间工作室 在那边工作
You could set up a studio and work there.
我不知道
I don't know.
还要知道什么？
What's there to know?
你结婚了吗？
Are you married?
什么？
What?
我才没有结婚
The last thing I am is married.
我是一根从零往后走的指针 两边空白
I'm a needle starting at zero going the other way, and double blank
突然间...
All of a sudden...
你这样的人出现了
someone like you comes along.
你不了解我 尼尔
You don't know me, Niel
我足够了解
I know enough.
跟我走
Come with me.
怎么了 宝贝？
What's wrong, babe?
没什么 事事都好 你会去吗？
Nothing's wrong. Everything's right. Will you go?
是的
Yeah.
好
Good.
亲爱的
Hi, sweetie.
你忘记妈妈会去接你吗？
You forget your mom was picking you up?
不是
No.
那是怎么回事？
So, what's going on?
我想独自一人
I felt like being alone.
来吧 我送你回家
Come on, I'll drive you home.
有何动静？
What's happening?
长官
Sir.
杰克森队长想知道有何动静
Captain Jackson wants to know what's going on.
没动静 不要用无线电
Nothing's going on. Stay off the air.
技术
Technique.
（IGM 投资高品位金属）
芝麻开门 就在那
Open Sesame. Right there.
就是他
There he is.
我们走！
We walk!
我快完事了
I'm there.
我们走！
We walk!
他听到了
He's heard it.
注意
Heads up.
- 出来一个 - 等一等 队长
- One's coming out. - Hold it, Captain.
文森特 他没带着任何东西
Vincent, he's not carrying anything.
我看见了
I see.
我们上
Here we go.
等我老板命令 他俩都没拿什么东西
Not till my boss says so. Both of them are not carrying anything.
让他们走
Let them go.
你什么意思？我们可拘捕他们
What do you mean? We can take them on!
什么罪名？你打算控他们什么罪名？
On what? What are you going to take them on?
破坏入口？ 他们还没偷什么
Breaking an entry?They didn't steal anything.
你不明白吗？
Don't you get it?
这只会被定为屁大点的轻罪 他们待半年就能出来
It gets knocked back to a misdemeanor, they do six months and they're out.
没他妈的门
No fucking way.
我不愿被我老板骂 就因为你放走他们
I'm not taking the heat from my boss.
他们不能走
They are not walking.
正是他们要做的 他们走 这是我的行动
That's exactly what they'll do. They'll walk. This is my operation.
我有战术指挥权 凌驾你的职级
I have tactical command that supersedes your rank.
他们会离去 你要让他们走 妈的！
They will walk away and you will let them. Fuck!
回去工作
Back to work.
洛城警方？G 搞什么？这把火他妈从哪儿来的？
LAPD, the G, what? Where the fuck did this heat come from?
也许是他们的一次行动 针对那个地方 不是我们
Maybe it's the score they were onto. The place, not us.
因为那里被劫过几次
Because it's been hit a couple of times.
假设他们盯上我们的电话 我们的房子
Assume they got our phones, our houses.
假设他们盯着我们 此时此刻
Assume they got us right here, right now...
当下 每一件事 假设一切
as we sit. Everything. Assume it all.
银行那事我们怎么给凯尔索付钱？
How are we gonna buy the bank package from Kelso?
我先垫付 那不是问题
I'll front that. that's not a problem
范桑特的75万呢？
What if Van Zant has 750?
范桑特？听着
Van Zant? Listen,
我们处于压力下 你想和范桑特来场街头世界大战吗？
with the heat we got, you want to play World War II on the streets with Van Zant?
不 我想问他要我的75万
No, I want my 750.
我比你们任何人更想搞范桑特 他他妈是个大富翁
I got more motivation to whack Van Zant than either of you. He is a fucking luxury.
我们的问题 是劫银行还是现在就开溜
Our problem is to take the bank, or split right now.
不回家 不收拾东西 什么也不要
Do not go home, do not pack, nothing.
现在起30秒后 我们各走各路 就这样
Thirty seconds flat from now, we are gone on our separate ways. That's it.
克里斯
Chris
银行值得冒险
The bank is worth the risk.
我需要它 兄弟
I need it, brother.
我们应该留下做完它 我出来就是为这个
We should stay and take it down. That's where I come out.
我跟你 尼尔 无论什么
I roll with you, Neil. Whatever.
- 无论什么 - 不 这次不行 迈克尔
- Whatever. - Not on this one.
这次 你靠自己决定
On this one, you're on your own.
你认为这是最好的做法吗？
You figure this is the best thing to do?
是最好的做法吗？
This is the best thing to do?
我已经有计划 事后我就走人 因此回报是值得的
I've got plans, I'm going away after, so the reward is worth the stretch.
但伊莲恩很照顾你 你有许多积蓄
But Elaine takes good care of you. You got plenty put away.
你有国库券 不动产
You got T- bonds, real estate.
如果我是你 我就聪明点 不碰这事
If I were you, I would be smart and cut loose of this.
对我来说...
For me...
行动就是美酒
the action is the juice.
我参加
I'm in.
提欧
Trejo
干 当然
Yeah, sure.
我们走
Let's go.
去他们的 我们干
Fuck them, let's do it.
我们走 我们有许多事要做
Let's go. We got a lot of work to do.
可以的话我会的
Well, I will
提姆 我给你打回去
Tim, I gotta call you back.
- 有什么事吗？ - 你是亚伦·马西亚诺吗？
- Can I help you? - Are you Alan Marciano?
对 你他妈是谁？
Who the fuck are you?
我是谁？
Who am I?
文森特·汉纳警督 洛城警局
Lieutenant Vincent Hanna, LAPD.
洛城？这儿是拉斯维加斯 你在这里没有司法权
LA? This is Las Vegas. You don't even have jurisdiction here.
你知不知道你他妈在推谁？我认识人
Do you know who the fuck you're pushing around? I know people here.
拉斯维加斯警方拘押你
Las Vegas PD takes you into custody.
你会被引渡到纽瓦克（新泽西） 因为走私香烟...
You are extradited to Newark on a warrant for smuggling cigarettes...
三年前 从北卡罗来纳...
up from North Carolina three years ago...
或者你跟我们合作
or you go to work for us.
简单明了
Cut and dried.
就是这样
That is it.
见鬼
Shit.
莎琳·施赫勒斯
Charlene Shiherlis.
谁？
Who?
你是什么 他妈的猫头鹰吗？
What are you, a fucking owl?
上周每天都和你在电话里淫声浪语的女士
The lady you been talking dirty to on the telephone every day last week.
好了 你知道吗？你不能把我和她扯上
All right. You know what? You can't tie me to her.
谁需要？你的屁股在回新泽西的飞机上 笨蛋
Who needs to? Your ass is on a plane back to New Jersey, jackoff.
哦 老兄 我只是...
Oh, man. I just...
我怎么会跟那婊子混在一起？
Why did I get mixed up with her?
因为她有个大屁股
Because she got a great ass!
你的脑袋一直在上面钻啊钻的
And you got your head all the way up it.
天啊
Jesus.
当我想起屁股...
When I think of asses...
女人的屁股...
a woman's ass...
便想起一些东西
something comes out of me.
那么？
So?
那么 没什么大事
So, no big thing.
我要的...
All I want...
是她丈夫和他的混蛋团伙
is her husband and his whole fucking crew.
你要和杜拉克警司合作
You'll work with Sgt. Drucker.
圣克莱门特路和赫摩萨
San Clemente Road and Hermosa...
我们在那儿穿过栏栅 那是通道
that's where we cut through the fence. That's the access.
对
Right.
这里的保安系统是个笑话
The security systems around here are a joke.
圣文森特托马斯桥 那是一号逃跑路线
St. Vincent Thomas Bridge, that's escape route number one.
路线二...
Number two:
在这边 是阿纳海姆往110公路
Over here. Anaheim to the 110.
好
Good.
明白吗？
You got it?
好的 走吧
Good. Let's go.
他们回头望向...
They were looking back...
这方向
in this direction.
集装箱设施？
A container facility?
什么？运输盗窃？
What? Cartage theft?
太明显了
Too visible.
对他们来说得益太少了
Too lowball for them.
有一家炼油厂和一家废料场
There's an oil refinery and a scrap yard.
炼油厂发薪用支票
Refinery pays by check.
没有现金
No cash around.
废料场也一样
Same for the scrap yard.
也许偷轮毂？
Stealing hubcaps?
炼油厂和废料场？
A refinery and a scrap yard.
是什么鬼玩意儿？
What the hell is going on?
正是我们正想搞清楚的
That's what we are trying to figure out.
我们以为已知道了
We thought we had it.
以为我们已知道了
Thought we had it.
我有个想法...
I got an idea...
他们在看些什么
on what they're looking at.
想知道他们在看什么吗？
Want to know what they're looking at?
我说 这人真行 他真行
I mean, is this guy something, or is he something?
这伙人很棒
This crew is good.
你们想知道他们看什么吗？
You want to know?
什么？
What?
我们
Us.
洛城警局
The LAPD.
警察局
The police department.
我们给人认出了
We just got made.
耶
Yeah!
好吧
Okay!
好吧 杂种
Okay, motherfucker!
凯尔索交来的？
Kelso come through?
对 凭这个你能盖一家银行
Yeah, you can build a bank with these.
姓汉纳
Name is Hanna.
名字 文森特
First name, Vincent.
我用五百元贿赂这个警司
I smeared this sergeant five yards.
汉纳全面监视你们
Hanna's all over you.
监视所有的工作车 迈克尔家 施赫勒斯家
He's on all the work cars. Michael's house. Shiherlis's.
没有你家 他们晚上跟丢了你
Not yours. They've been losing you at night.
他是条猛犬
He's a hot dog.
研究生 海军陆战队
Graduate school. Marine Corps.
抢劫及凶杀科警督
Lieutenant in Robbery- Homicide.
他拿下过一些大团伙 在芝加哥赶走了弗兰基
He's taken down some heavy crews. He blew away Frankie in Chicago.
他是个他妈的疯子
He was a fucking maniac.
那之前他做毒品工作
He was working narcotics before that.
离婚两次 现任妻子叫贾丝汀
Divorced twice. Current wife's Justine.
他就是格外施压的原因
He's why the extra heat.
那个副警司...
The vice sergeant...
说汉纳喜欢你...
says Hanna likes you...
认为你算某种明星 做这个厉害 做那个厉害
thinks you're some kind of star. You do this sharp, that sharp.
“看看这人多厉害 能想到这个”
"Look how sharp this guy is to figure that. "
他像心脏病般好笑
Funny as a heart attack.
三次婚姻？什么玩意儿？你觉得这说明他喜欢待在家里？
Three marriages? What the fuck? Do you think that means he likes staying home?
说明他是那种待在外面...
Means he's one of those guys out there...
整晚搜寻的人 敬业献身
prowling around all night, dedicated.
有他和这么多的压力 你应该取消
With him and this much heat, you should pass.
值得一试
It's worth the stretch.
这人可以成功或失手
This guy can hit or miss.
你一次也不能失手
You can't miss once.
你肯定吗？
You sure?
我肯定
I am sure.
我们去车房吧
Let's go to the garage.
我们去哪里？
Where are we going?
你去哪里？
Where are you going?
外出
Out.
他们用什么频道？
What are they on?
TAC 9.
他们出机场往北 在405公路
They're northbound out LAx on the 405.
我们有四个地面小组
We got four ground units.
我是18号机的文森特·汉纳
This is Vincent Hanna in Air 18.
线上是谁？
Who have I got?
我是JJ 40号机
This is JJ. I'm in Air 40.
理查德·格洛弗和我一起
Richard Glover's with me.
车在105公路东行...
It's on the 105 eastbound...
接近110公路
approaching the 110.
交替追踪？
Revolving tail?
对 我有两个组在前面 三个在后面
Yes. I got two units in front, three behind.
好 叫其中一个在佛蒙特匝道入口接我
Okay. Have one of them pick me up at the Vermont on- ramp.
我们走
Let's go.
我离他百码吗？太近还是太远？
Am I 100 yards, or what? Am I close or far, or what?
300码 中间车道
Three hundred yards, center lane.
你好吗？
How're you doing?
我请你喝杯咖啡如何？
What do you say I buy you a cup of coffee?
好 当然 我们走
Yeah, sure. Let's go.
跟着我
Follow me.
在福尔松待了七年
Seven years in Folsom.
单独囚禁三年
In the hole for three.
之前在麦克尼尔
McNeil before that.
麦克尼尔有传说的那么艰难吗？
McNeil as tough as they say?
你想当监狱学者吗？
You looking to become a penologist?
你想再回去吗？
You looking to go back?
你知道 我追捕一些团伙 那些想胡搞然后被抓回去的人
You know, I chased down some crews. Guys just looking to fuck up, get busted back.
那是你吗？
That you?
你一定追了些笨猪团伙
You must've worked some dipshit crews.
我追各种类型的
I worked all kinds.
你看见我抢劫酒铺 胸前刺着“天生失败”的纹身吗？
You see me doing liquor store holdup with a "Born to Lose" tattoo on my chest?
不 我没看见
No, I do not.
对了
Right.
我绝不会回去
I am never going back.
那就别搞什么行动
Then don't take down scores.
我做我最擅长的事
I do what I do best.
我搞行动 你做你最擅长的事：想法阻止我这样的人
I take scores. You do what you do best: Try to stop guys like me.
你从没想要正常生活？
You never wanted a regular type life?
那是他妈什么样？烧烤和球赛吗？
What the fuck is that? The barbecues and the ball games?
是的
Yeah.
这种正常生活是你的生活吗？
This regular type like your life?
我的生活？不 我的生活...
My life? No, my life...
我的生活是一片灾区
My life's a disaster zone.
我有个一团糟的继女
I got a stepdaughter so fucked up...
以为她的生父是个大型浑蛋
because her real father is this large- type asshole.
我有个妻子
I got a wife.
我们互不搭理 婚姻正在走下坡路 我的第三次
We're passing each other on the down slope of a marriage. My third.
因为我花费所有的时间在街头 追捕你这样的人
Because I spend all my time chasing guys like you around the block.
那是我的生活
That's my life.
有人曾对我说...
Guy told me one time:
“不要沾上任何30秒内不能摆脱的事物...
"Don't get attached to anything you can't walk out on in 30 seconds...
一旦你感觉的街角的危险”
"...if you feel the heat around the corner. "
如果你盯着我 我一动你就必须动...
If you're on me and you got to move when I move...
你怎能期望保住婚姻呢？
how do you expect to keep a marriage?
这是个有趣的观点
That's an interesting point.
你是什么人 修道士？
What are you, a monk?
我有个女人
I have a woman.
你怎么跟她说？
What do you tell her?
我告诉她我是推销员
I tell her I'm a salesman.
那么 如果你看见我从街角走来...
So, if you spot me coming around that corner...
你就从这女人身边走开？
you'll just walk out on this woman?
不说句再见？
Not say good-bye?
那是纪律
That's the discipline.
那相当空虚
That's pretty vacant.
正是如此
It is what it is.
就是这样 否则我俩还是干点别的吧 伙计
It's that, or we both better go do something else, pal.
我不懂做别的任何事
I don't know how to do anything else.
我也不懂
Neither do I.
我也不太想做
I don't much want to either.
我也不想
Neither do I.
你知道 我不断做一个梦
You know, I have this recurring dream.
我坐在一张很大的宴会餐桌边...
I'm sitting at this big banquet table and...
我调查的所有凶案受害人都坐在那里...
all the victims of all the murders I ever worked are sitting there...
他们用黑的眼珠子瞪着我...
and they're staring at me with these black eyeballs...
因为他们头部有八号球大的伤口出血
because they got eight- ball hemorrhages from the head wounds.
他们就在那 这些发胀的人...
And there they are, these big balloon people...
因为我发现他们时 他们已在床下两周
because I found them two weeks after they'd been under the bed.
邻居报称有恶臭...
The neighbors reported the smell...
他们就在那里...
and there they are...
全部坐在那里
all just sitting there.
他们说什么？
What do they say?
什么也没有
Nothing.
没说话？
No talk?
他们无话可说
They have nothing to say.
我们只是彼此望着对方
We just look at each other.
他们望着我...
They look at me...
就是这样 就是这个梦
and that's it. That's the dream.
我做梦自己遇溺
I have one where I'm drowning.
我得弄醒自己并呼吸 否则会死在睡梦中
I gotta wake myself up and start breathing or I'll die in my sleep.
你知道这什么意思吗？
You know what's that about?
还有...足够的时间
There...having enough time.
足够时间...
Enough time...
做你想做的事？
to do what you want to do?
正确
That's right.
你现在在做？
You doing it now?
没 还没有
No, not yet.
你知道 我们坐在这里...
You know, we're sitting here...
你和我 像一对正常的伙伴
you and I like a couple of regular fellas.
你做你要做的事 我做我要做的事
You do what you do, and I do what I gotta do.
既然我们曾经面对面...
Now that we've been face to face...
要是我在现场 必须撂倒你...
if I'm there and I gotta put you away...
我不会喜欢的
I won't like it.
但我告诉你...
But, I tell you...
如果是在你...
if it's between you...
和某个你要把他妻子变成寡妇的可怜虫之间...
and some poor bastard whose wife you're gonna turn into a widow...
兄弟...
brother...
你完蛋了
you are going down.
这枚硬币还有反面
There's a flip side to that coin.
若你把我逼入绝境...
What if you do got me boxed in...
而我必须撂倒你呢？
and I gotta put you down?
因为不管如何...
Because no matter what...
你不能挡我的路
you won't get in my way.
我们曾经面对面 是的
We've been face to face, yeah.
但我不会迟疑
But I will not hesitate.
一秒钟也不
Not for a second.
也许会是这样
Maybe that's will be.
或者...
Or...
谁知道呢？
who knows?
也许我们会永远不再见
Maybe we'll never see each other again.
他们甩掉了我们
They dumped us.
什么？
What?
他们甩掉了我们
They dumped us.
什么意思？
What do you mean?
克里斯溜走了
Chris slipped away.
他没谈及他们的行动
He doesn't talk about their scores...
所以我从马西亚诺那里没问出什么 我试过了
so there's nothing for me to get from Marciano. I just tried.
- 迈克尔·切里托呢？ - 一样
- What about Cheritto? - Same.
收发器放在一辆去圣克莱门特的公共车上
Transponders got put on a bus to San Clemente.
他们甩掉了我们所有的监视？
They dumped all our surveillance?
是的 同一时间 晚上九点
Yes, at the same time. 9:00 p.m.
我和麦考利一起喝咖啡 半小时前！
I had coffee with McCauley half an hour ago!
我们盯着你们 然后麦考利驶往机场
We were on you. Then McCaouley drives to LAX
监视组不能飞过去 因为航线限制
the surveillance can't fly over, because of the flight path
他的车还在那里 他不见了
His car's still there. He's gone.
谁有一丁点知道这些人他妈的在哪儿？
Does anybody have any idea where the fuck these people are?
他有联络吗？
Hear from him?
什么也没有 没联络更让我不安
Not a thing. And not hearing bothers me more.
这人在哪儿？
Where's this guy?
这里有个人...
This guy here...
我们雇用他
we put him on.
说他认识麦考利
Says he knows McCauley.
你是谁？
Who are you?
温格洛
Waingro.
我叫温格洛
My name's Waingro.
我日夜守在这间办公室里 你有多熟识他？
I've been living in this office day and night. How well do you know him?
我们一起做过些大行动
We took some major scores together.
为什么他一直没联系我？
Why haven't I heard from him?
现在他可能忙着
He's probably busy right now.
但他行事很彻底
But he's real thorough.
他不会忘记你的
He ain't going to forget about you.
真让人放心
That's very reassuring.
我有几招可以在这里用上
I got some moves I could make here.
可能对你会很有帮助
Probably be a big help to you.
认出那烤肉的人吗？
You recognize the grill man?
没
No.
福尔松
Folsom.
D区的 和杜比·拉什同一囚室
d-block. Housed with Dobie Rush.
我一直没能休息
I ain't got my break yet.
西斯科和潘乔没出现
Cisco and Pancho didn't show.
拖走垃圾 到后面拖地
Haul out the garbage. Mop up the back.
晚点休息吧
Take your break later.
人渣
Piece of shit.
拿走！
Pick up!
他到底在哪儿？
Where the hell is he?
我想查看一下工作车
I want to check the slot for the work car.
我也想
So did I.
别挂
Hang on.
嘿 用有线电话 打103-7206找我
Use the land line. Call me at 103-7206.
你在哪儿？
Where are you?
到处有警察监视我 伙计 像是跟屁虫
There's cops all over me, man, like a cheap suit.
我甩不掉他们
I can't dump them.
他们知道你看见他们吗？
They know you see them?
他们平行紧贴我
They're doing parallels.
我可以再试试摆脱他们
I can try to dump them again.
我们怎么知道你是否摆脱了？
How are we going to know if you did?
你会引他们来找我们
You'll draw them to us.
到文图拉去 带他们去那里
Go to Ventura. Pull them out of here.
好的 我很抱歉老兄 我最不想让你失望的
All right. Look I'm sorry man. Last thing I wanted to do was let you down.
拿走
Pick up.
尼尔 伙计 你好吗？
Neil, man. What's up?
你在这儿做什么？
What are you doing here?
我在找能应付无线电追踪的司机
I'm looking for a driver who can handle scanners on the radio.
现在 今天
Right now, today.
你还记得吗？
You remember the drill?
对 当然
Yeah, sure.
你行吗？
You cool?
你知道我行
You know I'm cool.
一个回答 做还是不做 就现在
One answer, yes or no. Right now.
做 老兄 去他的 算我一个
Yeah, man. Fuck, yeah. You're on.
五分钟后到后面
Out back in five.
是什么烧焦了？
What's burning?
是什么事？
What is this?
你想去哪里？
Where do you think you're going?
别动！手举起来！
Don't move! Put your hands in the air!
举手！
Hands up!
扔掉 快！
跪下！
Get on your knees!
给我钥匙
The keys!
跪下！
过那边去！
Get over there!
转身！
Turn around!
把手放在背后！
Put your hands behind you!
躺下！
Get down!
别动
Stay down!
趴下！
Get down!
- 趴下 - 钥匙！钥匙！
- Down! - The keys! The keys!
趴着别动
Stay down!
我们不想伤人 我们来要银行的钱 不是你们的钱
We want to hurt no one. We're here for the bank's money, not your money.
你们的钱有政府保险 你们不会损失一毛
Your money is insured by the government. You won't lose a dime.
想想你的家人
Think of your families.
别冒生命危险 别想当英雄
Don't risk your life. Don't try to be a hero.
现在我要你们坐在地上 手放头上
Right now I want you to sit on the floor, put your hands on your head.
有人感觉不舒服
Anybody feels sick...
有人心脏有问题 过去靠在墙上
anybody got heart trouble, go ahead lean against the wall.
给我钥匙
Give me the key.
什么钥匙？
What key?
坐好 别动
Sit down and stay down!
坐下 别动 让它淌血吧
Sit there. Don't move. Let it bleed.
坐下！
Get down!
头都低下！
Put your heads down!
伏下 低下 低下
Get down. Down, down, down.
低下头！
Put your heads down!
嘿 克塞尔
Hey, Kossel
你们在调查尼尔·麦考利的案子？
You guys working a case on a Neil McCauley?
有个线人休·本尼打电话说有一家银行 你们在查什么事吗？
This C. I. , Hugh Benny, called in about a bank. Are you looking out of something?
文森特！
Vincent!
远东国家银行！11:30！
Far East National Bank, 11:30!
我要在菲格罗亚和第五街设路障...
I want a block at Figueroa and Fifth...
我还要第六街往北弗洛尔设路障
and I want a block northbound Flower at Sixth.
他们已经出来了
They're already coming out.
好了 我们要在车上抓他们
Okay. We gotta take them in the car.
等他们全上车
Wait till they are all in.
开枪要干净 小心周围
Get clean shots. Watch your background.
警察！走开！
Police! Move!
闪开闪开 伏低
Move. Move. Get down.
走开！伏下
Move it. Down, down.
我们做到了 尼尔
We did it, Neil.
走开！
Move!
伏下
Get down!
操！操！
Fuck! Fuck!
上车！
Get in the car!
走！走走！
Go! Go!
走！
Go!
走
来 来
Come on! Come on!
快离开这里！
Ge the hell out of here!
趴下
Get down!
让开路！让他们趴下！快！
Out of the way! Get them down! Now!
过来
Come here.
我抱着你
I got you.
没事了
It's okey.
今天萨瑟兰街区的惨剧 一场银行劫案祸延街上
Tragedy in the Sutherland neighborhood today. A bank robbery spilled out into the street.
克劳迪娅·纽曼 现场直播 她带来最新消息 克劳迪娅？
Claudia Newman, live on the scene. She has the latest. Claudia?
今天下午 这个街区因一次出问题的银行抢劫而遭殃
This afternoon, this neighborhood was terrorized by a bank holdup gone wrong.
街上满是购物者和小孩 警方和武装劫匪...
With the streets full of shoppers and kids, police and armed robbers...
对不起 酒保
Excuse me, bartender.
今晚的重要新闻：抢劫 追击及最终死亡
Our top story tonight: Robbery, pursuit and, finally, death.
洛杉矶一条街道因银行抢劫而震动...
A Los Angeles neighborhood is shaken by a bank robbery...
以杀人及恐惧告终
that ended in homicide and terror.
一名嫌犯 迈克尔·切里托...
One suspect, Michael Cheritto...
是卷入这场被阻止的抢劫中的四人之一
is one of four men involved in the foiled robbery
- 死在现场 - 你来点什么 女士？
- died at the scene. - What can I get for you, miss?
同时受致命伤的：另一名疑犯 唐纳德·布里丹...
Also fatally wounded: ...another suspect, Donald Breedan,
- 死于枪伤...- 女士？
- who died of gunshot wounds...-miss?
当时警方和疑犯正大范围交火
during the extensive gunfire between police and suspects.
好了 按着他
All right, hold him.
没事的
It's all right.
怎样？
So?
他失血和休克
He's got blood loss and shock.
我给你四分之一格令的吗啡止痛 皮下注射
I'll give you quarter- grain bottles of morphine for the pain. Subcutaneous injection.
最低限度？
Bottom line?
主要是组织受损 那是好事
It's mostly tissue damage, which is good.
他的锁骨断裂 你们能休息一下吗？
His clavicle's fractured. Can you rest for a while?
6、7小时
Six, seven hours.
- 就这么多？ - 就这么多
- That's it? - That's it.
脱下衬衣
Take off your shirt.
什么？
What?
脱下衬衣
Take off your shirt.
这是女儿给我的
My daughter gave it to me.
我不管 脱下来
I don't give a shit. Take it off.
克里斯
Chris
听着 听我说
Listen. Listen to me.
奈德会来接你 他会送你到他那里
Nate's going to pick you up. He's going to take you to his place.
莎琳在哪？
Where's Charlene?
我们必须离开这里 6点钟新闻全是我们 我们必须离开这里
We gotta get out of here. We're all ouver the 6 o'clock news. We gotta get out of here.
没有她我不走
I'm not going without her.
考虑一下
Think about that.
我在奈德那儿见你
I will meet you at Nate's.
你去哪儿？
Where are you going?
我必须查查我们的逃跑路线 是否跟其它该死的事一样给泄露了
I gotta find out if our out got spilled along with every other damn thing.
谁干的？
Who did it?
谁不在场？
Who wasn't there?
提欧
Trejo.
在奈德家见
See you at Nate's.
你还要我吗？
You still want me?
你现在来这里接我 多明尼克和我
You come down here right now and you get me. Dominick and me.
好的 宝贝
Okay, baby.
我两小时后到
I'll be there in two hours.
好吧
All right.
上帝诅咒你 克里斯
Goddamn you, Chris.
上帝诅咒你
Goddamn you.
你坐飞机往洛杉矶
You're on a plane to Los Angeles.
是的
Right.
你为何这样做？出什么事了？
Why did you do it? What happened?
- 他们强迫我 - 谁？
- They made me. - Who?
安娜在哪？
Where's Anna?
她死了
She's dead.
迈克尔和代替你的布里丹也死了
So is Michael and Breedan, the guy who stood in for you.
谁干的？
Who did it?
他们抓了安娜 老兄
They had Anna, man.
谁抓了她？
Who had her?
温格洛
Waingro.
他一个人？
On his own?
- 替某个人 - 谁？
- For someone. - Who?
他替别人工作...
The other he worked for.
范桑特
Van Zant.
范桑特？
Van Zant?
对
Yeah.
你肯定吗？
Are you sure?
范桑特
Van Zant.
你跟他们说过我们怎样逃走吗？
Did you tell them how we're getting out?
我认为没有
I don't think so.
说吧
Come on.
我不记得
I don't remember.
我给医院打电话
I'll call a medic.
我挺不过去
I'm not going to make it.
我全无感觉
I can't feel a bloody thing.
我的安娜走了
My Anna's gone.
她走了
She's gone.
别这样扔下我 尼尔
Don't leave me like this, Neil
求求你 朋友
Please, homes.
别这样扔下我
Don't leave me like this.
你用移动电话吗？用固定电话
You on a cellular? Use a hard line.
这是新的
It's a new one.
这家伙住在恩西诺的山景台
The guy lives on Hillside Terrace, Encino.
10725号
克里斯呢？
Chris?
他和我一起 在我那里
He's with me, my place.
下一个 温格洛 好吗？
Next, Waingro, okay?
你有时间吗？
You got the time?
我会抽时间
I'll make time.
我要新的逃走路线
And I need a new out.
那些暴露了？
Are those blown?
我怎能信任呢？
How can I trust it?
好的 没问题
Okay, you got it.
保持健康
Stay healthy.
莎琳·施赫勒斯
Charlene Shiherlis.
杜拉克在威尼斯区有一座安全房可以藏她
Drucker's got a safe house in Venice to stash her in.
尼尔的逃亡系统
Neil's transportation.
这里的事办完 就打电话 某个地方 某人正在想法替他安排
After we've done here, get on the phone. Somewhere, someone's trying to put it together for him.
你不相信麦考利已经有路线了吗？
You don't believe McCauley already had get a way lade on?
他当然有 现在他需要另一个
Sure he did. Now he needs another.
要是你 今天下午之后你还能信任它吗？
Would you trust yours after this afternoon?
这告密的杂种 我们从哪得到他的？
This rat motherfucker, where did we get him?
他是个行窃案的线人 来报告劫银行线索
He's a C. I. For a burglary cop. Called in the tip on the bank.
说到尼尔·麦考利
On Neil McCauley.
我们还有多少时间？
How much time we got?
8至10小时 他要安排新路线 那以后 他就走了 拜拜
Eight, ten hours for him to set up a new out. After that, he's gone, bye- bye.
你向我们告发麦考利！你怎知道？
You ratted McCauley to us! How'd you know?
谁告诉你的？
Who told you?
谁告诉你的 告密的杂种？
Who told you, rat motherfucker?
谁？
Who?
温格洛 他在哪儿？
Waingro, where is he?
在哪儿？
Where?
我怎么能知道？
How the hell would I know?
这儿有些什么？
Well... what do we have here?
这儿漂亮吗？
This pretty?
漂亮吗？
你这坨屎
You slightly piece of shit.
你告诉我想脱离困境 你怕得要死 对吧？
Told me you wanted out from under. You're scared to death, right?
你想脱身吗？这是出路 莎琳
You want out? This is your out, Charlene.
对 你有何下场？
Yeah, what's your end?
我不需要笨妞
I don't need no stupid broad.
我怎会牵涉此事的？
How'd I get into this?
嘿嘿嘿 别闹
Hey, hey, hey, easy.
你听见我的话了 她生活坎坷
You heard me. She had a rough ride.
给她点喝的 到水槽上方的橱柜看看
Fix her a drink. Look in the cabinet above the sink.
去她的
Fuck her.
你最好进去 待在里面
You better get in there and stay in there.
看看这里
Lookie here.
我是杜拉克警司 洛城警局凶杀科
My name is Sgt. Drucker, LAPD Homicide.
要送多明尼克进卧房吗？
You want to put Dominick in the bedroom?
他和我待着
He stays with me.
那么 现在如何？
So, what now?
他说的对
Well, he's right.
因为你想脱身吗？这就是出路
'cause you want out? This is out.
你相信你得背叛克里斯吗？
You believe you have to betray Chris?
没门
No shit.
正是如此 你不得不如此
That's right. You would have to.
瞧 如果你不出卖克里斯 你就害了多明尼克
See, if you don't betray Chris, you victimize Dominick.
因为等你作为从犯入狱 他会成为孤儿
'Cause he becomes an orphan when you go to prison as an accessory...
因为你没有父母照顾他 所以他会被送到寄养家庭...
'cause you got no parents to take him. So he ends up raised in foster homes...
青少年中心
juvenile facilities.
之后他会偷车
Then he steals a car.
然后他就卷入“角斗学院” 就像山鸡和浩南
Then he winds up in gladiator academies like Chino and Tracy.
毁了一生
Fucked for life.
你知道会发生什么 因为你是过来人
You know what happens, because you've been there.
多明尼克还没机会选择他的生活 但克里斯选了
Dominick didn't get a chance yet to choose his life. But Chris did.
如果你交出克里斯 你就干净脱身
If you give up Chris, you get off clean.
你可以做到的...
You can do it...
为你的孩子 这样你能抚养他
for your kid, so you can raise him.
你还有什么要兜售？
What else are you selling?
各种的烂事
All kinds of shit.
但我用不着兜售 你知道的
But I don't have to sell this, you know it.
这种烂事自然而然
This kind of shit here sells itself.
好了 丹尼 最新消息
Okay, Danni, here's an update.
杜拉克在二线
Drucker's on Line 2.
警督 等一等
Lieutenant, hold on for a second.
警督 杜拉克警司在另一线上
Lieutenant, I have sergeant Drucker's on the other line.
会议通话吧
Conference him in.
说吧
Go ahead.
文森特 是我
Vincent, it's me.
一个回答 是什么？
One answer. What's it going to be?
我们准备好了 她会打电话
We're set here. She'll make the call.
好 很好 情况是这样
Okay, That's good. Here's the deal here.
休·本尼已改过自新...
Hugh Benny has reformed his wayward life...
成为重生的好市民
and become a born- again good citizen.
看起来 尼尔被一个叫温格洛的牛仔出卖给我们
Apparently, Neil got sold out to us by this cowboy named Waingro.
温格洛曾是尼尔团伙的一员
Waingro used to be a part of Neil's crew
后来替一个洗钱人工作 名叫范桑特
then went to work for a money launderer named Van Zant.
我们说话时 有小组在范桑特家中...
Units are at Van Zant's house as we speak...
因为他今晚较早前被射杀
because he got shot dead earlier tonight.
现在 如果尼尔要追杀别的人 那就温格洛
If Neil goes after anybody else, it's going to be Waingro.
温格洛刚拿到侯爵机场酒店的一间套房...
Waingro just got himself a suite at the Airport Marquis...
化名杰米森
under the name Jamieson.
他现在在那里 我要你把这消息告诉县里的...
He's there now. I want you to get that to bail bondsmen, bookies...
保释担保人、庄家、外派警员以及线人
assignment officers and snitches in County.
任何你想得到 会把消息传出去的人
Anyone you can think of who'll put it on the street.
派一组人到酒店
Deploy a team at the hotel...
并每30分钟亲自检查通讯
and personally check their coms every 30 minutes.
因为也许尼尔会去找他
Because maybe Neil will go for him.
好吗？你感觉如何？
Okay? How're you feeling?
吊着膀子 但我会活下来
Hang up, but I'll live.
好
Okay
他在这里
He's here.
尼尔还在这里
Neil is still here.
我能感觉到
I can feel it.
会留多久？
For how long?
七八个小时 最多
Seven, eight hours, max.
你干了什么？
What did you do?
那是你干的？
That was you?
那是我的工作 我不是卖金属的
That's what I do. I don't sell metal.
本来没事的 之后你飞过去 现在麻烦了
Would have been okay, you fly out after. Now it's jammed.
我们要一起走
We gotta go together.
那些人是和你一起的？
Those other people were with you?
我的朋友 迈克尔...
My friend, Michael...
他知道风险 他本不必去的
he knew the risks, he wouldn't have to be there.
常在河边走哪能不湿鞋
When it rains, you get wet.
收拾东西 我们走
Get packed. Let's go.
伊迪
Eady.
你为何这样对我？
Why did you do this to me?
不会有事的
Lt'll be all right.
明白吗？
Do you understand?
不会有事的
It's going to be all right.
这地址D层18单位有一辆科迈罗
There's a Camaro at this address, Level D, Slot 18.
这儿有些现金
Here's some cash.
什么时候结束？
When is it over?
现在起22小时
Twenty- two hours from now.
- 然后我们安全离开这里 - 你何时让我走
- Then we get out of here clean. - When will you let me leave?
现在就走
Go now.
你想出去？门在那边
You want out? There's the door.
你稍后会让我离去吗？
Will you let me leave later?
情况会不同
It will be different.
你还不明白吗？
Do you even understand?
准备好了
It's ready.
这是我的朋友拉尔夫
This is my friend Ralph.
你没说你已然...
You didn't tell me you were...
天啊！
Oh, my God!
萝伦呢？
Where's Lauren?
她在丽萨贝丝家
She's at Lisa- Beth's.
此事和我无关 我很抱歉
This has nothing to do with me. I'm sorry.
你有什么要抱歉？
What are you sorry about?
坐下
Sit down.
你都不生气吗？
Don't you even get angry?
我生气
I'm angry.
我很生气 拉尔夫
I'm very angry, Ralph.
你可以干我太太 只要她想让你干
You can ball my wife if she wants you to.
你可以在她的沙发上晃悠
You can lounge around here on her sofa.
在她前夫的...
In her ex-husband's...
死板科技后现代主义的扯淡房子中
dead-tech, post-modernistic, bullshit house...
若你想的话
if you want to.
但你不能看...
But you do not get to watch...
我他妈的
my fucking...
电视机
television set!
看在上帝的份上
For God's sake.
把电视机放下
Put the television set down.
我从对你不忠 婊子
I never cheated on you, bitch.
也许你应该
Maybe you should have.
- 我应该吗？ - 你与此有关
- I should have? - You're a party to this.
我要拉尔夫干你 因为这使我开心
I made Ralph fuck you because it makes me feel good.
我们的处境荒谬
Our situation is absurd.
住口 拉尔夫！坐下！
Shut up, Ralph! Sit down!
为什么我要理清事情 还要向你解释？
Why is it that I have to figure things out and explain them to you?
我心口如一 而且言出必行
I say what I mean, and I do what I say.
多么可敬
How admirable.
- 一点没错 - 可就是不谈和我们有关的
- You bet. - Except none of it's about us.
是的
No.
我可能是抽大麻或兴奋剂迷糊了
I may be stoned on grass and Prozac but...
但你像个死人走出我们的生活
you walk through our life dead.
现在我还要自贬 找拉尔夫终断和你的关系
Now I have to demean myself with Ralph just to get closure with you.
护照、旅行支票、信用卡
Passports, traveler's checks, plastic.
这飞机...
The plane...
在洛杉矶机场包机站17号机库
charter terminal, LAx, Hangar 17.
呼号是“1011山岭”
Call letters are 1011 Sierra.
降落...
Touches down...
等你五分钟然后便起飞
holds for you five minutes, then splits.
飞机经得起航空局的检查 飞行计划什么的
The plane will stand an FAA check. Filed a flight plan, the works.
克里斯在哪？
Where's Chris?
他走了
He's gone.
什么？
What?
说他要自己走 去找莎琳了
Said he's going on his own. Went to find Charlene.
- 是你带他来这儿？ - 对 我带他来了
- Did you bring him here? - Yeah, I brought him here.
怎么回事？
What happened?
这是个自由国家 老兄
It's a free country, man.
九点联络我...
Check in with me at 9:00...
确保一切妥当
everything is still cool.
好的
All right.
我再也不知道自己在做什么？
I don't know what I'm doing anymore.
我知道生命短促
I know life is short.
能活多久是运气
Whatever time you get is luck.
你想走？
You want to walk?
你现在走...
You walk right now...
全凭你自愿...
all on your own.
你自愿选择跟我
On your own you choose to come with me.
我只知道...
All I know is...
我再到任何地方去也没有意义
there's no point in me going anywhere anymore...
如果我会独自一人...
if it's going to be alone...
没有你
without you.
我有个活的
I got a live one.
我不挂线
I'll hold.
现身
Show yourself.
- 快做 - 住口！
- Do it. - Shut up!
只需在窗前站一秒
Now, just one second at the window...
就全都了结了
and it's all over.
嘿伙计...
Hey, man...
你知道这附近有地方出租吗？
you know any place to rent around here?
杂货店墙上有招租告示
不是他
It's not him.
不是克里斯
It's not Chris.
第二组 这是指挥部
Unit 2, this is Command.
截停他 查看身份
Take him at the street. Check him out.
他叫约翰·彼得森
He's John Peterson.
有效的身份证 车辆登记人是...
Valid ID. Car's registered to...
布科夫斯基 吉恩
Bukowski, Gene.
向运输署查核过
Ran it to DMV.
没有不妥
It's clean.
让他走
Let him go.
收到
Roger.
谢谢 晚安
Thank you. Have a good evening.
此路不通 文斯
It's no- go, Vinc
我们等时你想喝咖啡吗？
Would you like a cup of coffee while we wait?
好 这样最好
Yeah, that would be nice.
你有什么消息？
What do you got?
没事发生
Nothing's happening.
喂 是文森特
Hello, it's Vincent.
有何动静？
What do you got?
没有什么事 温格洛去拿冰
Nothing's going on. Waingro went for ice.
就这样
That's it.
你们知道吗？
You know what?
尼尔走了
Neil is gone.
像鸟儿般飞走
Flying like a bird.
文森 你怎知道？
How do you know?
我们仍然有诱饵
We still got bait!
也许某个时候
Maybe some time!
我们有什么？
What do we got?
一路平安 杂种
Bon voyage, motherfucker.
你很不错
You were good.
我到酒店去
I'm going to the hotel.
我要冲个澡
I'm going to take a shower...
然后睡上一个月
and I'm going to sleep for a month.
来
Here.
醒来吧
Come on.
操
Shit.
他妈的浪费
Motherfucking waste.
浑蛋们他妈的成天冲自己开枪
Assholes shoot themselves all fucking day.
不是你 宝贝
Not you, baby.
不是你
Not you.
她会在哪儿？她叫萝伦
Where would she be? Her name is Lauren.
萝伦·古斯塔夫松 她该在这儿的
Lauren Gustafson, and she's supposed to be here.
我要人帮忙...
I need somebody to help...
我抱着你
I got you.
你会没事的 我发誓 没事的 宝贝
You'll be all right, I swear. It's okay, baby.
找医生来！
Let's get a doctor!
来个医生！
Let's go! A doctor here!
- 那是你妈妈 - 冷静下来
- There's your mama. - Let's just calm down.
- 她服用药物吗？ - 我很冷静 没有
- Is she on any drugs? - I'm calm. No.
找创伤外科及血管外科来
Get a trauma surgeon and a vascular surgeon.
我觉得她割断两条动脉 我几乎摸不到她的脉搏
I think she cut both arteries. I could hardly feel her pulse.
她的血压下降
Her pressure's down.
呼吸也是 你要给她插管
So is the respiration. You have to intubate her.
准备好了
It's ready.
别人最后一次见她是什么时候？
When's the last time anybody saw her?
我不知道
I don't know.
你在哪儿找到她？
Where did you find her?
浴缸
The bathtub.
给她注射大针管的生理盐水
Give her large- bore normal saline.
紧按出血点
Keep pressure on those bleeders.
给我两公升 O型血 查出她血型和输血
Give me two units, O- negative. Let's type and cross her for six.
呼吸专家呢？我们需要帮忙 让他们过来
Where is respiratory? We need more help. Get them down now.
ｘ光准备 插管后照胸片
Let's have x- ray ready for post- intubation chest x- ray.
你女儿出了手术室 她在恢复室 好吗？
Your daughter's out of surgery and she's in the recovery room. Okay?
她生命体征稳定
Her vital signs are stable.
外科医生几分钟后出来跟你们谈 到时你们就知道怎么回事了
The surgeon will be out to speak to you in a few moments. Then you'll konw what's going on.
她没事吧？
She's okay?
她做得不错
She's doing good.
她会没事的
She'll be okay.
她不会有事
She's going to be okay.
我的宝贝 她为何这样对自己？
Oh, my baby. Why did she do this to herself?
看看她做的 看看她对自己做的
Look what she did. Look what she did to herself.
没事的 会没事的
It's all right. It's going to be all right.
我在这儿 不会到别处去
I'm here. I ain't going anywhere.
明白吗？我不会到别处去
Do you understand? I ain't going anywhere.
是我
It's me.
飞机已在空中 你正准时
Plane's in the air now. You're right on time.
我仍找不到可信任的司机
I still can't find a driver...so that's in the trust.
还有一事...
One other thing...
我得告诉你
I gotta tell you.
你要的人在候爵酒店 化名杰米森 如果你还在乎的话
The guy you want is in the Marquis under Jamieson, if you still give a shit...
我想你不会在意了
which I figure you wouldn't.
你想得对
You figured right.
再见 兄弟
So, so long, brother.
你不要着急
You take it easy.
你成功在望
You're home free.
不要着急
Take it easy.
怎么了？
What is it?
没什么
Nothing.
成功在望
Home free.
我必须料理一些事情
I gotta take care of something.
有时间吗？
Is there time?
有时间
There's time.
我很快回来 让车子开动吧
I'll be right back. Just leave her running.
入住登记
Registration.
客房部
This is room service.
有个杰米森要了三明治 但房号弄错了 是什么？
A Jamieson ordered a BLT, and they screwed up his room number. What is it?
- 他们经常这样 - 我知道
- They're always doing that. - I know.
1735.
谢谢
Thank you.
请注意
Your attention, please.
现时响起火警警报
We are currently experiencing a fire alarm.
不用惶恐
Do not panic.
不要乘坐电梯
Do not take the elevators.
我留在这儿
I'm staying here.
我查看楼梯 若有烟便会要你走
I'll check the stairs. If there's smoke, I'll pull you out.
她爸爸呢？我该通知他吗？
What about her dad? Should I call him?
他在塞拉斯某处
He's somewhere in the Sierras.
她选上你
And she chose you.
她选择你那里
She picked your place.
这是不对的 发生在她身上的
It's not right, what happened to her.
是的 不对
No, it's not.
是否有方法...
Is there any way that...
可克服我们间的问题？
it could work out between us?
我希望能说有 你知道
I wish I could say yes, you know.
可是...
But...
到最后...
in the end...
就像你说的...
It's like you said:
我沉迷于...
All I am...
追捕我的罪犯
is what I'm going after.
我不是你想要的人 贾丝汀
I'm not what you want, Justine.
走吧 如果你必须走
Go on, if you have to.
我会留下
I'll stay.
我没事 我可应付
I'm okay. I can handle this.
小心些
Just be careful.
给我电话让我知道你没事
Call me here. Let me know you're okay.
好吗？
Okay?
保安 三层发生火警
Security. There's a fire on three.
我们必须疏散各楼层
We have to evacuate all floors.
我不能离开这里
I can't leave here.
我们何不先谈一下 兄弟？
Why don't we just talk about this a bit, brother?
他在十七楼
He's here on 17.
望着我
Look at me.
望着我！
Look at me!
洛城警局！别动！
LAPD! Don't move!
手放在头上！
Put your hands on your head!
把我转到五频道
Switch me to TAC 5.
卡萨斯...
Casals...
JJ...
杜拉克 JJ
Drucker, JJ...
我在大堂层 接近楼梯井
I'm in the lobby level by the stairwell.
有什么事？
What have you got?
各小队正在乘其它电梯往十七楼电梯
Teams are moving up the other elevators to the 17th- floor elevators.
因为火警全都不能使用 到处是人
All out of commission because of the fire alarm. People everywhere.
好的 10- 4
Fine. 10- 4.
把枪给我
Let me have that shot.
跟你说过我绝不会回去的
Told you I'm never going back.
是的
Yeah.